Welcome to the call from we take your ipos provider you have an online order from the website
But it seems like the system is offline and you haven't received the order
Yeah
Okay, so which
Sorry
Yeah, for you for the online stuff
Yes, yes, you have an online order and the system is offline. That's what you haven't received it
When?
Actually the order is for 1120
Today
Yes, it is for tonight
What did you order?
You want me to tell you the order products
Yeah, can I just check it out for you one second
I'm already sent the order details of the owner's WhatsApp. I'll read them for you two second
So have you turned the system off yourself or you have an internet connection problems at the
shop?
I don't know really it's a it's a boss boss is no here just now
He just popped out for for 5 10 minutes
Maybe maybe from back in 10 minutes you speak to him about online stuff, please actually
I think you can help me with the system if you just restart the ipos system
Probably
Close down and I have no idea how to touch it to be honest 10 minutes from back
He will speak to you. We have to tidy up just now and it's very late. Oh
Okay, then that's what I'll call you in 10 minutes again. Okay. Thank you. Bye. Bye. Thank you. Thank you