Can we take your ordering system provider?
Yeah, did you get my message that people are saying they're trying to order online and they can't do it through the web?
Okay, so there is only one reason if they can't order and that's because they are out of the delivering area.
We can add more push goods if we can deliver to them.
No, no, no, no, there's well in, it was well within, it was only two minutes away from the place.
Okay, so it wasn't far out, it was just two minutes away.
The first order of the night didn't come through properly either.
I mean, there was trouble in the last night.
There's been sort of ongoing problems that never seems to go smoothly with this machine.
So, is that the printer issue?
No, it's not been a transition.
It was a transition issue earlier on tonight.
But then somebody phoned the actual work phone to make an order.
And they said that they couldn't, the app kept cutting them out.
What did cut them out?
Yeah, well, they couldn't complete the order on the app.
Okay, on the app or website.
Okay, let me just log into your website and app and see if I can place a test order.
Just a second, I'll send both a collection order and the delivery one has a test.
Please check it out from your site and see if you received them at the shop.
Right, okay.
You're getting printed.
Yeah, do that, that's great.
I will do that, okay?
So, let me just stay on the line or you can give me time so I can place the orders and get back to you.
Yeah, okay then, thanks.
Okay, I'll do that.
Thank you, bye-bye.
Yeah, bye-bye.